SANDHYA MALLIDI

sandhyamallidi19@gmail.com | 9985488153

Results driven team leader with comprehensive experience in handling medical data. Managing, assessing, reporting and Quality check of all medical information using safety database. Excellent communication and organizational skills utilized in leading a team responsible for generating and disclosing timely and accurate information to both internal and external recipients.

SKILLS

Good medical terminology Good verbal and written communication skills Ability to meet deadlines Solid team player with very good interpersonal skills Excellent teamwork and time management Small and large group leadership and communication

EXPERIENCE

SPi global technologies, Chennai

Aug 2014 - Jan 2017

Designation: Technical Analyst-Biomedicine

Department: Scientific Publishing

- Worked for "Embase" Elsevier.
- Systematic screening of biomedical literature for adverse drug reactions.
- Capturing all potential and unanticipated health risks for a drug from the international biomedical literature, also allows
 pharmaceutical manufacturers to proactively develop more effective drug safety strategies.
- Embase helps track all published/peer-reviewed biomedical information on products and makes it easy to quickly review reported safety risks, side effects and adverse drug events information.
- Comprehensive and up-to-date drug safety information.
- The Embase thesaurus, Emtree (dictionary), is one of the most comprehensive thesauri available for life science information, with a unique focus on drug terminology.

Freelancer for the SPi global technologies (Embase)

Jan 2017-Aug 2017

Pulsus (Omics International), Hyderabad, India

Sep 2017 – June 2018

Designation: Quality Control Executive **Department:** Scientific Publishing

- Publishing all scientific research papers
- Quality check and assessment of research papers
- Reviewing and proof reading all scientific medical research papers

Contract Employee for the SPi global technologies/Straive (Embase)

July 2018- Present

Natco Research Centre (sanath nagar, Hyderabad, India)

Jan 2014- July 2014

- Internship in Drug Regulatory Affairs
- Drug Master File, Drug registration guidelines and approval process in Europe

EDUCATION

Shri Vishnu College of Pharmacy (M.Pharmacy)

Pharmaceutical Management and Drug Regulatory Affiars

CGPA: 7.94

Bhimavaram, AP 2012-2014

Pydah College of Pharmacy, (kakinada)(B.Pharmacy)

CGPA: 7.50

Kakinada, AP 2008-2012

Diploma in Pharmacovigilance

Hyderabad

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full Name: Mallidi Sandhya Spouse Name: Pratap Reddy DOB: 19-10-1990 Languages: English, Telugu